Unable to change
A compulsive action,
something one must fulfill
Even though we were no longer a couple
During the Christmas days we had borrowed your dad's house by the sea
While he was with his new fiancee in Roslagen
A gray palace overlooking Krokvik's boat docks,
the little bird island, and then the empty, vast, horizon
I stood out at the beach edge and filmed the sea with my iPhone
A documentary film about sand
The house was really far too big for a lonely man
When the gin first rose in the body we felt happy
See so gray the sea is
So gray and motionless
An endless smooth surface
One can miss it for dirty steel
When it subsided, we felt a great fatigue come
The empty twilight light
The next day took the flight from Landvetter to de Gaulle
It was a strange New Year
Everything was abandoned
We looked up at the sky but saw no fireworks
We had sex in the hotel room
To take in felt strange
I saw a documentary about a French man
that went with dog sledding, or what is called,
From Russia to China
He traveled over huge white plains
We drank wheat beer out of can
We must have fallen asleep at last and when we woke up
showed the TV a talk show led by a child
We dressed up and went out in the cold
The business was closed
Wrapped in lethargy
A borderland between intoxication and ignition
We walked close to each other, shoulder toward shoulder,
But we had already begun the huge work to forget,
to erase,
to give way to the new one that would rush out of us
Yes, that was a difficult question.
I have said before that I wrote the book
in the explicit and the purpose of
Make Kungsbacka a mythological place.
But I mean that I want to make it a
That it was not in the municipality, so to speak,
in Kungsbacka municipality.
So this became a way to make it literary, kind of.
A great deal is autobiographical and
An yet crucial part of fiction.
It places itself somewhere in between,
As I think many books do.
But is like
Not completely loyal with any of the so to speak.
It is not entirely loyal with the autobiographical,
But it is not completely fictitious either
Another favorite author that I have
Is Roberto Bolaño
that has written some kind of directory text
Over different people
and things like that
And my book is also some kind of catalog of Kungsbacka.
The three I tried to bake into something "west coast".
Right now, Carina Rydberg is actually reading, in fact, reading Carina Rydberg
The highest throw.
It has started well, I have not come that far.
I'm reading it right now.